This is the car that broke down last time, right?
这是上次那台出故障的车对吧
It's been repaired
已经修好了呢
yes
是啊
Oh, that's great. I'm so lucky.
哎呦  太好了  真是庆幸
I see you guys are going out, so be careful on the road.
我看你们好像要外出  那路上小心
Then let's do this first
那先这样
us
我们
How bad is the current situation?
现在的状况有多不妙
Well, this is also the first time I've encountered this.
这个嘛  我也是第一次碰到
Shouldn't I be trapped here forever?
该不会永远被困在这里吧
Can't we go back?
我们回不去了吗
No way
才不会呢
Don't worry, just fix it. It can be fixed.
你别担心  修好就行  可以修理好
Just fix it. Just fix it.
只要修好就行了  修理好就可以
It'll be fine if it's fixed. It can be fixed.
修好就没问题  这可以修好的
Let's go home first
我们先回家再说
this time before
之前这段时间
I don't think there's any need to ask anything in particular.
我都觉得没有必要特别过问
Because the existence of a time machine is ridiculous in the first place.
因为时光机的存在原本就很不像话
no matter who made it
不管是由谁制造而成
Or even from the magic lamp
或甚至是从神灯里蹦出来的
I don't think it's a big deal
我都觉得没什么大不了的
This shouldn't be made by you, right?
这应该不是你制造的吧
So where did this one come from?
那这台是从哪冒出来的
I picked it up
我捡到的
Turns out I picked it up
原来是捡到的
You actually
你竟然
I actually picked up a time machine
竟然捡到了一台时光机
The time machine turned out to be picked up
时光机竟然是用捡来的
He actually said he picked up a time machine
他竟然说自己捡到一台时光机
Jiongwan
炯万
Please don't mention my husband's name easily
请你不要轻易提到我老公的名字
There is no need for us to meet with the chairman in the future.
我们跟理事长以后没有见面的必要
please leave
请你离开
I told you to go quickly
我叫你快走
sorry
对不起
I'm really sorry for you
我真的很对不起你们
It is my fault
是我错了
It's me who didn't teach my son well
是我没把儿子教好
will harm you
才会害你们
Lost a precious child just like that
就这么失去了宝贵的孩子
I also know no matter what
我也知道无论如何
I can't even get your forgiveness
都无法得到你们的原谅
I can't give you any comfort
也没办法给予你们安慰
I will hold the mood of atonement
我会抱着赎罪的心情
Spend the rest of your life
过完下半辈子
I will definitely let myself
一定会让自己
Tortured every minute
每分每秒都饱受折磨
sorry
对不起
can you really do it
你真的能做到吗
You really have a way
你真的有办法
Will you live a life of torture?
一辈子都过着饱受折磨的日子吗
i will do that
我会那么做
I will let myself live like that
我会让自己那么活着
I'm really sorry for you
我真的很对不起你
That bastard thing
那个混帐东西
I hope they are a family
我希望他们一家人
Can live in dire straits for the rest of his life
能一辈子过着水深火热的日子
No matter how incompetent your child is,
就算自己的孩子再怎么不成材
But I have to uncover the child’s scars with my own hands
但要亲手揭开孩子的疮疤
How difficult is it
究竟有多困难
I know it too
我也心知肚明
I'm grateful to you for that.
就这点来说  我很感谢你
even so
即便如此
Fortunately, I have a place to come back to.
还好有个能回来的落脚处
How about we just get drunk today?
我们今天要不要干脆喝个烂醉
Anyway, there’s nothing left to do tonight
反正今天晚上已经没戏了
- Eat more - Okay
- 多吃点      - 好的
I thought it was all fixed
我还以为都修好了
It turned out not to be the case
结果却不是这么回事
It's not all bad
倒也不全然都是坏事
Anyway, once I go back
反正一回去
Have to go to work soon
马上就得去上班
At least if you continue to stay here
至少继续待在这里的话
You don’t have to suffer that 6:30 in the morning
就不用受到那个早上6点30分
35 minutes 40 minutes
35分  40分
The alarm that rings every 5 minutes is disturbing.
每5分钟响一次的闹铃干扰啊
Not bad
还不赖
I can also see my mother in her youth a few more times
还能多看几眼年轻时期的妈妈
Take more breaths of fresh air
多吸几口新鲜空气
Hagfish even sells for only 2,000 won
黏盲鳗甚至只卖2000韩圜
You can’t even come up with 2,000 won
你连2000韩圜都拿不出来
Are you trying to draw a clear line with me now?
你现在这是要跟我划清界线吗
Aren't you still here?
不是还有你在吗
In fact, the money I prepared is almost gone.
其实我准备的钱也差不多快用完了
Because I didn't plan to stay so long
因为我原先没有打算待这么久
I didn't expect to be trapped here either.
也没料到会被困在这里
Mark Six Lottery
六合彩
Don’t you have the winning numbers memorized?
你没有背好的中奖号码吗
What do you think
你觉得呢
hateful
可恶
What a useless conscience
真是派不上用场的良心
It doesn't matter
没关系
Anyway, we are all able-bodied
反正我们都四肢健全
We even know the future direction
甚至还知道未来的走向
You can definitely make a lot of money if you make up your mind.
下定决心肯定能就赚大钱
Are you still afraid of starving to death?
难不成还怕饿死吗
but
不过
How could the time machine be picked up?
时光机怎么可能是捡到的
Even walking on the roadside
就连走在路边
It’s hard to find 500 won coins
捡到500韩圜硬币都很难
I'm also very curious about this matter
这件事我也很很好奇
Then how did you pick it up?
那你是怎么捡到的
It was a day of pouring rain
那是个下着倾盆大雨的日子
You've gone off course
你已经脱离行车路线
Searching again
正在重新进行搜寻
Not only did the navigation fail that day,
那天不只导航失灵
My vision was blurry because of the rain.
因为雨势的关系  眼前一片模糊
I was on the road where I didn't even know where I was.
当时在连我都不清楚是哪的路上
Been driving for a while
开了好一阵子
Then we met
接着就碰到了
Just in front of the old bridge
就在那座旧桥前方
Is it like being thrown in there?
就像被扔在那里吗
The car door is still open
车门还开着呢
There was even a sign in the car that said
车里甚至还放着写有
Tell me to drive across the old bridge ahead or something like that
要我开过前方那座旧桥之类的指示
and instructions for use
以及使用方法的说明书
I want you to drive past the one in front of you
要你开过前方那座
It's like I'm waiting to be discovered
就像是希望被发现  在等的感觉
Now that I think about it, that's not the only thing that's strange.
现在回想起来  奇怪的不只这一点
The day I bumped into you
我撞到你的那一天
Do you remember what you asked me?
你还记得问了我什么吗
That question about the phone
有关电话的那个问题
This is not a car that can hit just about anywhere.
这不是随便能撞到哪里的车
Did you call anyone?
你是不是跟谁打了电话
You must have been beaten
打了  你肯定打了
Usually inattentive while driving
通常开车时不专心
Isn't it more likely to cause an accident?
不是更容易出事故吗
What's strange
哪里奇怪了
Actually that day
其实那天
Someone really called me
真的有人打给我
yes
是
What did you say
你说什么
Only you can solve this matter from beginning to end
这件事自始至终  就只有你能解决
But I had no idea at the time
但我当时毫无头绪
I just dismissed it as a strange call and ignored it.
只当作是通奇怪的来电没在意
But no matter how I thought about it later, I felt that
但后来再怎么想都觉得
That's not what someone who knows nothing would say.
那不是一无所知的人会讲的话
Who could that person be?
那个人会是谁呢
I don't know either
我也不知道
Are you OK
你没事吧
The pace of walking is a bit strange
走路的步伐有点奇怪
I'm fine
我没事
You can’t apply for insurance claims here anyway.
反正这里也不能申请保险理赔
It seems this is not the first time I have heard this sentence
这句话我好像不是第一次听到
I'm fine
我没事
If I die here
要是我在这里丧命
Things will become quite difficult to understand
事情就会变得相当难解
I felt really confused at that time.
当时真的觉得很茫然呢
But to be honest, I'm not that confused now.
但老实说现在已经没有那么迷惘了
Because there is someone I want to be with
因为有了想待在一起的人
if
要是
If it's true
要是真的
Never find a way back
永远找不到回去的办法
I have to be trapped here for the rest of my life.
得一辈子困在这里
I seem to be able to accept it, too.
我好像也能接受呢
If you were with me
如果有你陪着我的话
Really
真的吗
how about you
那你呢
me
我吗
It’s useless to say more
多说无益
Of course not
当然不愿意
It seems that your words and deeds are a little different from yesterday.
你好像跟昨天有点言行不一呢
what do you mean
你指什么
Didn't you say you don't care?
你不是说不在意吗
Didn't you say that if I were here?
你不是说要是有我在
Are you willing to stay here all your life?
就愿意一辈子待在这里吗
I thought the back of my head
我还以为我的后脑勺
A hole is almost being seen through
快被看穿一个洞了
How many hours do you plan to stay here and watch?
你打算待在这看几个小时啊
no
不是啊
I'm just curious if things are going well
我只是很好奇事情顺不顺利
A person who is simply curious
单纯好奇的人
Will you sigh when you see me tilting my head?
会一看到我歪头就叹气吗
It seems that I am the only one who is sincere.
看来只有我是真心的呢
Of course I really mean it too.
我当然也是真心的啊
But now that it’s like this
但既然都这样了
It would be better to meet in 2021
干脆在2021年见面会更好啊
Can we still rely on modern civilization
还能依赖现代文明
Sorry, I won't watch it anymore
对不起嘛  我不会再看了
But can you leave the door a crack?
不过你能不能把门留个缝
knew
知道了
I know, I'm leaving now
我知道了  我这就走
I'm going in
我要进去了
This book has been selling very well recently
这本书最近卖得很好
- Really? - Yeah
- 真的吗      - 是啊
- It must be interesting. - That's right.
- 肯定很有意思      - 没错
- Do you want to buy a copy and take it back? - Okay
- 要不要买一本回去      - 好啊
Oh, thank you. Welcome back.
哎呦  谢谢你们  欢迎再来
- Thank you, you're welcome
- 谢谢      - 不客气
I've already seen it
我已经看过了
I think it looks good
觉得很好看
Your writing is not bad
你的文笔还不错
Please sign your name on the cover for me later
以后帮我在封面上签个名
Are you feeling better?
你的身体有好一点了吗
It's okay now that I'm here
有  我现在没事了
That lunatic should have been caught sooner
那个疯子真该早点被捉到
but
不过
Why don't you come to school since you've been discharged from the hospital?
你都出院了怎么不来上学
Is it because of our relationship?
难道是因为我们的关系吗
it's not like that
不是那样的
Then it's time to go to school
之后就该去学校了
Come back soon
快回来
Teachers and classmates are waiting for you
老师跟同学都在等你
Thanks
谢谢
See you at school then
那我们学校见
Meet Lee Soon Ae at school
在学校见吧  李顺爱
In the past, I only heard them asking me to meet at school.
以前只要听到她们约我学校见
I feel so scared
就觉得好害怕
It seems like it really doesn't matter now
现在好像真的没关系了
that's great
那真是太好了
correct
对了
I've prepared a gift for you
我准备了礼物送你
Is it the official printed version?
是正式上市的印刷版呢
"Lee Soon Ae"
“李顺爱”
The name is also printed clearly
名字也印得一清二楚
sign your name for me
帮我签个名
Signed long ago
早就签好了
Open the first page and take a look
你打开第一页看看
"To my best friend"
“致我最要好的朋友”
"Only my Y Yunying"
“只属于我的Y  允英”
Thank you
谢谢你
Really thank you very much
真的很谢谢你
This is the greatest gift in my life
这是我人生最棒的礼物
Do you really know something before you fix it?
你是真的懂点什么才在修理吗
If that were the case, I would have fixed it long ago.
要是那样的话  我早就修好了
How does that go
事情怎么样了
The rest of the procedure should go smoothly.
剩下的程序应该会很顺利才是
The chairman seems to have given an explanation
理事长好像也有交代
Make him admit everything and pay the price
要他承认一切付出代价
It seems that's what he told your dad.
他好像是这么跟你爸说的
The chairman is having a hard time now
理事长现在很辛苦
What else is needed at this time?
这种时候哪还需要别的呢
What we need most is family.
最需要家人啊
But from now on he will be left alone
但以后就独留他一人了
Why do you open the door so wide?
怎么把大门开那么大
Haijun
海俊
Haven't you seen what people outside are doing?
没看到外面的人做的那些吗
What should you do if someone comes in and hurts you? It's too dangerous.
有人进来伤到你怎么办  太危险了
Who else in this village can be better than my son?
在这村庄还能有谁比我儿子
More dangerous
更危险呢
I thought you had gone back
我以为你已经回去了
Thought you had enough of yours
以为你受够了你的那些
The so-called family members who do all kinds of evil
所谓无恶不作的家人
Just leave without saying goodbye
就这么不辞而别了
I would have done this if I could
如果可以  我本想这样做的
thank you for not doing that
谢谢你没那样做
I always hope to see you one last time
我一直希望能和你见最后一面
Don't you hate me?
你不讨厌我吗
Because of me, you are going through things that you don’t have to go through.
因为我你经历着本不用经历的事情
Don't even know how long this will last
甚至不知道这将会持续多久
Just because I'm worried that you might think this way
就因为担心你会有这种想法
So I want to meet you again
所以我想再和你见一面
Want to tell you I'm okay
想告诉你我没事
On the contrary, thank you very much
反而很感谢你
I really want to tell you this
真的很想告诉你这些
Thanks to you
多亏了你
Now I can at least make things right
现在我至少还能改正一切
Really sorry
真的对不起
Let you see my shameful appearance
让你看到了我丢人的模样
I'm still thinking
我还在想
How long do I need to wait before I can tell you this?
需要等多久才能告诉你这些
Fortunately I could tell you 30 years in advance
幸好能提前30年告诉你
What a blessing
真是万幸
where did you go
你去哪里了
Went to meet someone
去见了一个人
Why are you so listless?
为什么这么无精打采
us
我们
Can be done in the blink of an eye
可以在眨眼间
span 30 years
跨越30年
But it made me realize
但这让我意识到
Some people have to endure it
有的人则是要忍受
every day for these 30 years
这30年中的每一天
Did you go to see your grandpa?
你去见你爷爷了吗
I'm not regretting what we did
我并不是在后悔我们做过的事情
I know and understand
我知道  也能理解
Maybe this will be our chance
也许这将是我们的机会
Although we can't go back right now
虽然我们现在不能马上回去
But that means more time here
但这意味着有更多时间能留在这里
How about spending time like we didn't have before.
度过我们以前没有过的时光  如何
"A time we didn't have before"
“我们以前没有过的时光”
In other words, the time that I wanted to have but couldn’t.
或者说想有  但没能如愿的时光
Because I saw them again 30 years later
因为再次见到他们是在30年后
So create a beautiful memory for them
所以为他们创造一段美好的回忆
It should be fine
应该没事吧
do you like fishing
你喜欢钓鱼吗
i know a good place
我知道一个好地方
But I don’t want to go alone
但不想一个人去
Do you know what my original dream was?
你知道我原来的梦想是什么吗
Live an ordinary life and have an ordinary job
过着平淡的生活  有着平淡的工作
alone after retirement
退休后一个人
Just spend your whole life fishing leisurely like this
就这样悠闲地钓钓鱼  过完一生
Are you alone
一个人吗
Don’t you have family or children?
没有家人和孩子吗
may be
也许是吧
Too
也是
For you
对你而言
My family is not impressed
家人没什么好印象
But something seems to have changed now
但现在好像有点变了
I hope someone can stay with me
希望有人能陪在我身边
We can talk and laugh together
可以一起谈笑风生
You can also ask for help
还可以嘘寒问暖
I also want to live that kind of life
也想过那种生活
Of course life is like that
当然了  生活就是那样
You can definitely have that life
你绝对可以拥有那种生活
can i really do that
我真的可以吗
of course
那当然了
If you decide you want to live that life
如果你决定想过那种生活
I will do my best to help you
我会尽我所能帮助你
Then I beg you
那我就恳求你
"Plea"
“恳求”
Reduce your alcohol intake as soon as possible
趁早把酒量减少
If you don’t want to take those nasty medicines all the time
如果不想一直吃那些讨厌的药
Remember to eat on time
记得按时吃饭
Start regular health check-ups after 8 years
8年后开始定期做一次健康检查
OK
好的
Just no more worries
只有没了任何担忧
Only then can I live a life of talking and laughing
我才能过上谈笑风生的生活
Apart from these things that are good to me
除了这些对我好的以外
Didn't you ask me to do it for you?
没有要我为你做的吗
Just take me fishing occasionally
偶尔带我来钓鱼就行
The first time I went fishing was with my seniors after I joined the company
第一次钓鱼是我入职后和前辈一起
Found it suits me very well
发现很适合我
At that time, I thought it would be great to know earlier.
那时就觉得早点知道该多好
If you feel good today
如果今天你觉得不错
You can bring me here early
可以早点带我过来
The real fun is night fishing
真正有趣的是夜钓
You can also cook ramen and eat it
还可以煮拉面吃
alright
好了
- Here you go - Thank you
- 给你      - 谢谢
Blow it
吹一下
That's good
那样很好啊
But is this enough?
不过  这样就够了吗
that's enough for me
对我来说这已经足够了
Oh my god float
天啊  浮漂
Grandpa, I told you to wait a while
爷爷  我说过要等一会
But the float has moved
但是浮漂已经动了
Didn't move at all
根本没动
The beauty of fishing is to be patient and let it go
钓鱼的美妙之处在于耐心  放下吧
Okay, we'll come back when we get there.
好了  我们到达那边后再返回来
The last person to arrive wants to buy spicy rice cakes
最后到达的人要买辣炒年糕
Then let's go
那么  出发
Even the foul is so cute
连犯规都这么可爱
What are you doing
你在做什么
I won't
我不会
What should I say louder?
什么  大声点说
I can't ride a bicycle
我不会骑自行车
You two go ahead and leave me alone.
你们两个去吧  不要管我
How can I not ride a bicycle at this age?
这把年纪了怎么可能不会骑单车
Why didn't your father even teach you this?
为什么你爸爸连这都没有教你
He can't ride either
他也骑不了
His legs are a bit inconvenient
他的腿有点不方便
Yeah
是吗
if
如果
If he's okay
他没事的话
Do you want to teach me this too?
会不会也想教我这些呢
As a father, who doesn’t want to teach his children to ride a bicycle?
身为爸爸谁不想教孩子骑单车
Whenever I see
每当看到
He must be very sad that someone else is teaching their children.
别人在教他们孩子  他一定很伤心
I would think "I really want to teach"
会想着“我也好想教”
"I really want to teach my daughter"
“好想教我女儿”
do not worry
不要担心
Let me teach you
由我来教你吧
Put your feet on the pedal first and put them up first
先把脚放在踏板  先放上去
Then step hard and don’t have any worries
然后用力踩  不要有后顾之忧
Even if you shake and feel like you're going to fall
即使你摇晃  感觉要跌倒了
You must never stop and keep moving forward.
你也绝对不要停下  继续往前走
What if I do fall?
如果我真摔倒了呢
No, I'll be right behind you, don't worry
不会的  我就在你后面  别担心
let us start
我们开始吧
Don't let go suddenly, don't let go
千万不要突然放手啊  别放手
Oops, her exercise cells are too bad, right?
哎呦  她的运动细胞也太差了吧
This is her first time riding. You should keep supporting her.
她这是第一次骑  你应该一直扶着
How can I let go?
怎么可以放开呢
To learn well, you have to train rigorously from the beginning
要学好就得一开始严格训练
What are you talking about?
你在胡说八道什么
What to do if you leave a scar
如果留下了伤疤怎么办
I was wrong and sorry
我错了  对不起
Hate
讨厌
- It makes me sad. - I was wrong.
- 真让我伤心      - 我错了
- Do you know you are wrong - I was wrong
- 知道错了吗      - 我错了
I thought why it was so strange
还以为为什么这么陌生
It turns out this is time I've never spent before
原来这是以前我从没有度过的时光
- Do you know that you are wrong? - I know that you are wrong.
- 知错了吗      - 我知错了
in my changed future
在我改变的未来中
Can record more
能记录下更多一点
Is this kind of memory?
这种记忆吗
The little frog is singing
呱呱呱呱  小青蛙在唱歌
Children, grandchildren, and daughters-in-law gathered together
儿孙媳妇齐聚一堂
It would be nice if that was the case
如果是这样就好了
It would be great if that was really the case
如果真的是这样就好了
The Yunying one
允英  那个
Do you want to take a bite of the long rice cake?
你要吃一口长条年糕吗
No need for me to do it myself
不用  我自己来
I'll feed you
我喂你  来
Open your mouth quickly
快张嘴
Just accept his apology.
就接受他的道歉吧
Just say it doesn't matter. Really?
就说没关系了  真是的
How delicious is it?
怎样  好吃吧
I feed you, so it tastes better, right?
我喂你吃  所以更好吃吧
It's inherently delicious
是本来就好吃
The rice cake is chewy and delicious.
年糕很有嚼劲  真好吃呢
Who is he and why is he at the door of our Teacher Yin’s house?
他是谁  为何在我们尹老师家门口
probing
探头探脑的
Didn’t I ask you not to come for a while?
我不是要你暂时别来了吗
Why are you here?
怎么在这里
I know you are having a hard time now, how could I not come?
明知你现在很辛苦  我怎能不来呢
In the past I have also suffered
过去我也受到了
Chairman, you are very helpful.
理事长你很多帮助啊
- Please come in. - Thank you very much.
- 请进吧      - 好  谢谢你
Can you let me know before you leave?
你离开前能通知我一声吗
OK I will
好  我会的
Okay, then I'll wait for your news
好  那我就等你的消息
Okay, come in quickly
好  你快进去吧
Oops
哎呦
What should I do with that car?
该拿那辆车怎么办
We finally met here
我们最终还是在这里见面了呢
Who are you
你是谁
so sad
真让人伤心
I thought you would recognize me right away
还以为你会马上认出我
Don’t you remember my voice?
不记得我的声音吗
“This thing starts and ends.”
“这件事自始至终”
"Only you can solve it"
“就只有你能解决”
old bridge telephone
旧桥  电话
What did you say?
你说什么  喂
Only you can solve this matter from beginning to end
这件事自始至终  就只有你能解决
I knew you would remember
我就知道你会记得
because you are smart
因为你很聪明
It only takes 5 seconds to solve the twisting dice
还只要5秒就能解出扭计骰
Do you know who I am
你知道我是谁吗
How could I not know
我怎么会不知道
Where is my father?
我的父亲呢
What did you say
你说什么
I miss your dad very much
我很想你  爸爸
But are you giving me the time machine I gave you?
不过  你是不是把我送你的时光机
broken
弄坏了
Are you happy going fishing with your grandpa?
你跟爷爷去钓鱼还开心吗
Um
嗯
Come with me next time too
下次也跟我一起去吧
I also learned to ride a bicycle now
我现在也学会骑单车了
The scenery we went to today is very good
今天去的地方风景很好
So I want to go with you again
所以想跟你再去一次
Is that where it won’t be in 2021?
那是在2021年没有的地方吗
There should be
应该有吧
Has the car been repaired?
难道已经修好车了吗
Maybe
应该吧
Had known so
早知如此
I won’t make an appointment with them to see you tomorrow.
就不跟他们约好明天再见了
There's no need to go back now
不用现在回去也行
No
不
Anyway, we are the ones who can’t appear here.
反正我们是不能出现在这里的人
No matter what, it has to disappear
不管怎样都要消失才行
And we will meet again soon after we go back
而且回去之后很快就会再见面
And you
你呢
Is it really okay to go back like this now?
现在这样回去真的没关系吗
how could you
你怎么会
know i'm here
知道我在这里
Sorry to come to you suddenly
对不起  突然来找你
I won't tell anyone else you're here
我不会跟其他人说你在这里
I will also forget it from now on
从今以后我也会忘掉的
can i sit down
我能坐一下吗
Do we really have to send the child away after he is born?
孩子出生后  真的要把他送走吗
Send it to Chairman Yoon Byeong-qiu
送到尹炳球理事长那里去
right
对
I already said I would do this
我已经说过会这么做了
Because you think that child is scary and disgusting?
因为觉得那孩子很可怕很厌恶吗
right
对
All right
好吧
Then live a good life
那你好好过生活
Don't feel any guilt
不要抱着什么罪恶感
Forget everything and live your life
忘掉一切过日子吧
Don’t I understand your difficulties very well?
我不是很清楚你的苦衷吗
It's understandable that you would feel disgusted and frightened.
你会感到厌恶可怕也是情有可原
So if you feel very painful
所以如果觉得很痛苦
You don’t have to live with your children
可以不必跟孩子一起生活
i can understand
我可以理解
Chairman Yin Bingqiu
尹炳球理事长
Very rich and a good man
很富有  也是个好人
This is also a good thing for children
这对孩子也是件好事
Living in a rich family has everything you need
生活在有钱人家  样样不缺
This is how he will be raised
他会这样被养大的
I won’t feel resentment towards my mother.
不会对妈妈感到怨恨
There will be no complaints
不会有埋怨
He will grow up like this
他会这样长大的
Lie
骗人
How could you not blame me?
怎么可能不埋怨我
How could you not resent me?
怎么可能不怨恨我
I abandoned him
我都抛弃了他
After all, I am a mother who abandoned her children
我终究是个抛弃孩子的妈妈
Just believe me
你就相信我吧
Didn’t you say your name is the same as mine?
不是说名字跟我一样吗
That kid's thoughts will be similar to mine.
那孩子的想法会跟我差不多的
real
真的
will it be so
会如此吗
It was you who brought him into this world
是你让他来到这个世界上
This alone is a favor enough
光这点就已经是足够的恩惠了
He would think so
他会这么想的
Are you in a good mood?
心情舒坦吗
Um
嗯
This time it’s my turn to send away the person who abandoned me
这次换我送走了把我抛弃的人
I feel inexplicably relaxed
心情莫名轻松呢
Then you can really go back now, right?
那现在真的可以回去了  对吧
right
对
But it was really repaired this time, right?
不过这次是真的修好了吧
Should I go back to see the chairman again?
该不会又要回去见理事长吧
Will not
不会的
Because this time a real repairman showed up
因为这次出现了真正的修理工
Has anyone been here?
有谁来过吗
The person who called me under the old bridge at that time
当时  在旧桥下打电话给我的人
That's the person who built this time machine.
也就是制造出这台时光机的人
I couldn't believe it at first
起初我也难以置信
I don't think that person can exist
我认为那个人不可能会存在
How can it be
怎么可能
how could i
我怎么会
How can I have a son?
怎么会有儿子吗
You will obviously die in 2022
你明明在2022年就死了
Because you're not dead at all
因为你根本没死
Although it is true that he almost died
虽然说是真的差点就死了
But he survived in the end
但最后还是活下来了
Because there is a key there that you have overlooked
因为那里有一个被你忽略的关键
appeared in that hidden future
在那个隐藏的未来里出现的
it's me
正是我
I always wanted to give you another chance
我一直想再给你一次机会
An opportunity to make different choices
一个可以做出不同选择的机会
And you
而你
Sure enough we did it
果然做到了
There is a future there that I don’t know about
在那里有我所不知道的未来
These things happened because of that future
因为那个未来  才发生了这些事
So who is that person?
所以那个人是谁
secret
秘密
Are you really not going to say it?
你真的不说吗
Let's go
走吧
Just one step away now
现在就差一步了
yes
是啊
Thanks to some unknown benefactor, I can go back
多亏某个不知道的恩人可以回去了
There were still a lot of good times during this period, right?
这段时间还是有不少美好时光吧
There must be a lot of grateful moments
应该是有不少令人感激的时光
It's also because you are here
也是因为有你在
But after going back
不过  回去之后
Will this really change?
这一切真的会有所改变吗
What should I do if I leave it intact?
如果原封不动的话该怎么办
Go back quickly to confirm
赶快回去确认吧
are you ready
准备好了吗
See you in the future
是  未来见吧
Well, see you in 34 years
好  34年后见吧
- Hello - Has Haejun arrived safely?
- 喂      - 海俊  平安抵达了吗
I kept you waiting for a long time
让你久等了吧
I arrived grandpa
我到了  爷爷
good
好
Pick it up quickly
快接吧
Hello
喂
Is mom really you?
妈妈  真的是你吗
That's how we are
我们就这样
Back to the future safely
平安地回到未来了
our present
我们的现在
Really changed a lot
真的改变了很多
Home
家
changed
变了
Yunying
允英
This guy
这家伙
Really
真是的
where have you been
你到底去哪里了
I went to see my mother
我去看妈妈了啊
What
什么
What is she talking about?
她在说什么啊
Waiting for me to disappear without a trace
等待消失地无影无踪的我
Parents who have been waiting for a month
等了一个月的爸妈
Worried me to death
担心死我了
Became what I had seen in my dreams
成为了我曾经在梦里见过的模样
- Smelly girl - don't hit her
- 臭丫头      - 不要打她
For more than thirty years
长达三十多年的岁月里
He who is always waiting for me
始终等待着我的他
Didn't forget our agreement
没有忘记我们的约定
Haijun
海俊
but me
而我
Finally met the writer of my dreams
终于与我梦寐以求的作家相遇
became her editor
成了她的编辑
Mother
妈妈
I think this sentence needs to be deleted.
我看这一句还是得删掉
I do not want it
我才不要
If you want to review the manuscript like this
你要这样审稿的话
Just write your own novel
干脆自己写小说
Acting stubborn again
又在耍固执了
He's becoming more and more stubborn
越来越固执了呢
I mean, go ahead and write your own novel.
就是说啊  你自己去写小说吧
Wife
老婆
Do you want to give it to her?
要不要给她呢
for you
给你
Quite interesting
挺有趣的啊
Don't make trouble
不要闹
besides
还有
Dad, please be quiet and stop playing.
爸爸  安静点  别弹了
I loved last Sunday at 9pm
我喜欢上周日晚上9点了
Hello everyone, viewers
各位观众大家好
What you are watching now is "KSBC 9 o'clock news"
现在收看的是《KSBC  9点新闻》
Under investigation Songhuan Group Chairman Zhao Mingshi
正在调查松环集团会长赵明石
Prosecutors suspected of bribery
贿赂嫌疑的检方
Today, for Songhuan Group Corporation
在今天针对松环集团总公司
and 8 related companies to launch seizures
及8个其相关公司展开扣押
Looks similar
长得好像啊
The biggest doubt is to transfer company funds
最大的疑惑是为了转移公司资金
Hee-seop
熙燮
elder brother
哥
Hello uncle
大伯好
There are no guests today
今天没什么客人啊
This is a retro bar, so
这是复古酒吧嘛  所以
- Mastered 4 billion won - Dad
- 掌握到40亿韩圜      - 爸爸
size of funds
规模的资金
Evidence of transfer to the name of Chairman Cho Myung-seok
转到赵明石会长名下的证据
The details will be reported by reporter Kim Woo-hyun
详细内容交由金宇炫记者播报
Let's go
走吧
It feels so strange walking here, right?
走在这里的感觉好陌生  你说是吧
Feel better
感觉更棒吧
Hold hands whenever and wherever you want
随时随地想牵手就牵手
Don’t be afraid of speaking
讲话也不用有所顾忌
By the way, did your parents say anything when they saw me?
话说  你爸妈见到我没说什么吗
How could I not say it?
怎么可能没说
Whenever they see the news they say
每当他们看到新闻就会说
You look a lot like their old school teacher
你和他们以前学校老师长得很像
Even the sound is exactly the same
甚至连声音都一模一样
I feel incredible
觉得很不可思议
Your daughter is also quite suspicious, right?
你这个女儿也蛮可疑的吧
They were indeed suspicious
他们的确有起疑
Let's get started
开动吧
OMG the long rice cake looks so delicious
天啊  长条年糕看起来真好吃
come to you
来  给你
- Oh my god. Please use this.
- 天啊      - 这给你  请用
Eat
吃吧
It really tastes the same as what I’ve had before.
真的和以前吃过的味道一样呢
We were with Yunying at that time
那时候我们和允英一起
The same day I was riding a bicycle in the park
在公园骑单车  那天也是
It’s been 30 years
都过30年了
There's a friend your mother still misses
有位朋友仍让你妈念念不忘
That's why I named you after her
所以才会用她的名字为你取名
I can't stand it
真受不了
But you look more and more like her as you get older
不过你随着年纪长得越来越像她
I never thought something like this would happen
没想到还会有这种事
It should have been when you were pregnant with me
应该是怀着我的时候
I think of that friend often, maybe it’s like that
经常想起那位朋友吧  可能是那样
- Is it is it
- 是吗      - 是吗
Oops
哎呦
Do they believe what you say?
他们相信你那番话吗
What if I don’t believe it?
不相信又能怎样
Even if we are the same as those 34 years ago
就算我们跟34年前的
Teacher and friend look exactly the same
老师和朋友长得一模一样
They never thought it was because of time travel
他们也想不到是因为时光旅行
A while ago
前阵子
I met that person by chance
我还偶然遇到那个人
You won't do anything to yourself
你不会对自己的所作所为
Do you regret it?
感到后悔吗
Regret
后悔啊
If you like it, just say you like it.
喜欢就说喜欢
If it hurts, just say it hurts
会痛就说痛
If you're envious, just say envy.
羡慕就说羡慕
If only I were more candid too
如果我也再坦率一点就好了
Because I couldn't do that
因为我没能那么做
Because it's too late
因为为时已晚
Maybe I will live forever
或许我将会一直过着
The days of wandering among the crowd
在人群中徘徊的日子
It's never too late
绝不会嫌晚
Because now
因为现在此刻
To you in the future, it’s the past
对未来的你而言是过去
Is that so?
是那样吗
Although I don't know how she is doing now
虽然我不清楚她现在过得如何
but i think maybe
但我想也许
she has become more outspoken
她已经变得更坦率了
but me
而我
Still living on the same side
仍旧一边生活
While thinking about the future and the past
一边思考着未来与过去
good night, see you tomorrow
晚安  明天见
- It's been a lot of fun today - Yeah
- 今天真好玩      - 是啊
I can't look closer
我不能靠近一点看
My mother's face?
我妈的脸吗
Let's talk about it later. If you see it now, you'll be in trouble.
以后再说  现在就看到会有麻烦
Why
为什么
It wouldn’t be fun if the ending was spoiled.
被剧透结局就不好玩了啊
For the sake of our future relationship
为了我们日后的恋情着想
Sure enough, people who are destined to meet will eventually meet.
果然命中注定相遇的人终究会相遇
After all, my parents meet again here
毕竟爸妈在这里再次相遇
fall in love again
又再次相爱
yes
是啊
As far as you know, what's her favorite thing?
就你所知  她最喜欢什么
Now that you know everything, give me some tips.
既然都知道了  就给我点提示吧
So that I can prepare the gifts I will give later
好让我准备之后要送的礼物
It's you
是你
What my mother likes most in the world is you
在这世上  妈妈最喜欢的就是你
And the bouquet of flowers you occasionally give her
还有  你偶尔会送她的一束花
That really made her happy
那真的让她非常开心
- what is this - a gift
- 这是什么      - 礼物
I love so much
我很喜欢
I love it
超喜欢
Are you too easy to dismiss?
你太好打发了吧
This little thing makes you so happy
这点小东西就让你那么开心
I already have this gift from you, why should I give it to you again?
我已经有你这个礼物  何必再送呢
- That's - my gift.
- 那倒是      - 我的礼物
Is that time machine no longer usable?
那台时光机已经不能再使用了吗
I can only run back and forth one more time
只能再来回跑一趟
Anywhere
去哪里都行
Did you know that tomorrow is May 16th?
你知道明天是5月16日吗
It seems we think the same thing
看来我们想的一样
if
假如
What if I just make this trip?
假如就跑这么一趟
how do you feel
你觉得如何
It should be worth a try this time
这次应该值得一试
Let's go one last time
我们再去最后一次吧
I have to try my best this time
这次可要尽全力了
just in case
万一
What to do if variables occur
出现变数怎么办
Maybe the "future" will find us
也许“未来”会找到我们的
Because we will be together no matter what
因为无论如何我们都会在一起
Our meeting was not by chance
我们的相遇不是偶然
But it is the fate that we must meet
而是必然会相遇的命运
- Are you ready? - Okay
- 准备好了吗      - 好了
lets go
出发吧